Izzy: You can do this.
Pamela: Oh, hey, Izzy! Good luck!
Izzy: Thanks, Pamela.
Pamela: What time’s the interview?
Izzy: It’s at four p.m.
Pamela: Are you nervous?
Izzy: Well, a little bit.
Pamela: Don’t worry! It’s going to be fine. They’re going to love you.
Jenny: Ben. Ben. Can you hear me? I’m driving.
Ben: Yes, I can hear you, Jenny. Is everything OK?
Jenny: Ben, listen. It’s your sister. She had an accident this morning. I’m going to the hospital now.
Ben: Emma? An accident? Is she OK?
Jenny: A car accident. You need to come home today. I bought you a plane ticket.
Check your email. You’re on the eight o’clock flight this evening.
Ben: Is she OK?
Jenny: Ben? I can’t hear you. The signal’s really bad.
Ben: Jenny, I can’t hear you. Is she OK?
Izzy: OK. I think this works here, but maybe…What about this?
Ola: Yes, I like that.
Max: Did you say something?
Izzy: No, nothing. I think it was the door.
Ben: Hey, Izzy. I hope the interview went well. Listen, I got some bad news from home.
My sister, Emma, was in a car accident. I’m going back to the US tonight.
I’m on the eight p.m. flight from Gatwick Airport. I’m on my way to Victoria Station. Call me.
Ben’s voicemail: This is Ben. I can’t take your call, please leave a message.